more verb phrases
Narrator: 13
A: buy a pizza
Narrator: 9
A: call a taxi
Narrator: 1
A: dance the tango
Narrator: 11
A: draw a picture
Narrator: 2
A: find a parking space
Narrator: 6
A: forget somebody’s name
Narrator: 21
A: give somebody flowers
Narrator: 19
A: hear a noise
Narrator: 8
A: help somebody
Narrator: 3
A: leave your bag on a train
Narrator: 22
A: look for your keys
Narrator: 18
A: meet a friend
Narrator: 15
A: paint a picture
Narrator: 5
A: remember somebody’s name
Narrator: 17
A: run a race
Narrator: 7
A: see a movie
Narrator: 24
A: send a message
Narrator: 12
A: sing a song
Narrator: 25
A: swim in the ocean
Narrator:16
A: take a photo
Narrator: 10
A: talk to a friend
Narrator: 14
A: tell somebody a secret
Narrator: 20
A: try to open a door
Narrator: 23
A: use an app
Narrator: 4
A: wait for a bus